[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 4, "question": "Has he ever been in love?", "qSentId": 3}, {"answer": "I'm a fairly peaceful, docile individual.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "How do you feel about being called a genius?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "It's funny, I have no recollection of doing that so probably two or three years old.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "You were how old when you did these draws?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "She's ready to make Shaquille O'Neal's day, it looks like.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "What is she doing?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Probably about four, I guess.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "At what point did you go from gentle cartoonist to an evil person?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "The absurd, absolutely.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "You see the absurd and slightly sinister in everything?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "I guess with a Rick Perry or a Michele Bachmann it would be the best possible thing to happen to comedy.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Are you thrilled because it gives you great material?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Probably, yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Is that the dream double ticket?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "In 2011, yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Do you fundamentally like their policies?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Stewie.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Can you tell me who that is?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "I just screwed up your card.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "It's the basic math adds up, it adds up, right?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "No idea.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Do you think that Obama can win the next election?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "I struggle to find one.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "What's the left-wing equivalent of the tea party, would you say?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "That's what I'm told.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Not very proper.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "When you watch that, what do you think?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Have you always had an absolutely clear idea of what you were going to do in animated form?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Your contract is believed to be over $100 million.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "I guess if it's believed to be so that makes it true in America.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Are any of these allegations true?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Yes, that's what my lawyers tell me.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Was that a denial?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "If there's a Republican president, I will just keep getting richer.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Are you motivated by it?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Look, if I was, you know, Taylor Lautner walking around, I would have --", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "You have a problem getting a girl?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "As much as the next guy.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "How many times have you been turned down?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Maybe.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Is it the lines you're using?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "You just did.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Can I say that on CNN?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "Well, I was animation major in college.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "How did do you that?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "You didn't know?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Your mother broke it to you?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "ACFARLANE: My mother was always the first person to know gossip.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "How did you react?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Really, really -- certainly from a comedy standpoint, you know, just invaluable.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "How important was she to your career?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Yes, she was unflappable.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "There is not a mother in the world that would not be offended by something that you have done and you're sitting here telling me that your mother went along with all of this?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Yes, there are some things off limits.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Do you have any lines?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Well, we wouldn't make a -- we wouldn't make a 9/11 joke for at least two weeks after 9/11.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "That is just your gut.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "And how far do you tread?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Is religion a particularly sensitive issue?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "ETER: Oh, so Saddam Hussein did this?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "The Iraqi Army?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Some guys from Iraq?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "No, Peter, Iraq had nothing to do with this.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "That one lady who visited Iraq that one time?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "A combination of two things: I was -- I was giving a lecture at my college the night before, and went out with some of the faculty afterwards and had a few pints.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Does any part of you shudder at your own shocking humor?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "This last one was pretty -- was -- I mean, it was -- it was dark, but it was definitely fun.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Which has been your favorite, because you've done a few now?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "You know, it's funny.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "What do you -- what do you make of Charlie?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Well, what I would say was that the joke was about Charlie.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "How would you feel if a member of Amy Winehouse's family watching that was really upset and actually phoned you to say, what were you doing making jokes about Amy?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "The part that -- I -- oh, absolutely.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Would you be uncomfortable?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Not -- no, I actually haven't.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Have you had those calls?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "It's a great story.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Well, how do you know about that?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Never mind how I know these things.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "How did you find out about that?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Did you -- did you grovel pathetically?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "I tried.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Stand your ground like a man?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "I mean, it's -- if I say yes, he's going to crucify me on his show every night for a year.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "I mean, there's a certain irony in Jon Stewart ringing up, haranguing you for mocking him, isn't there?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Wrong to not see the funny side?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Probably.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "What are you schizophrenic, or what is this?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "ORGAN: I heard this, his original one, yes?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "I have -- I enjoy many different pursuits.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Isn't that the next obvious step?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "But, finally, I'm told that you had a very exciting new addition to your \"Family Guy\" cast list.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "How about the new Morey Amsterdam?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "Yes, it turns out -- yes, yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Is this right?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "I'm 6'4\".", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "What should people know about this guy from Wales?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Well, Simon had approached me about four years ago to work on a project which I couldn't do because I was under contract with a different channel.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Everyone is thinking who are -- how did Steve Jones get to be the host of the hottest new show on TV in America?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "About two years ago, yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Two years ago?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "I'm just going to do the best I can do on the show.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "he needs nipping in the bud?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Let's rewind.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "What was that picture that just came up?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "What a little nerd.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "What was that picture?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "That is me as a child in my bathers.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "What's that?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "That reminds me of a story my mother used to tell ex- girlfriends when I used to take them to meet my mother.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Do you still wear those?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "It's not on the mantle piece.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "Talking about that particular part of your anatomy, do you still have a plaster cast of it on your mantle piece at home in Wales?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "Well -- I'll be.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "They must be crawling around Sunset Boulevard, aren't they?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "Yes, and more.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "Is it all you hoped it would be?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "She's a good friend of mine, yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "Was it true?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "She's a friend of mine.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "Hayden Panettiere?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "ONES: I interviewed her once.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 744, "question": "Halle Barry?", "qSentId": 743}, {"answer": "Yes, I think there will be a lot of people not be asking who is Steve Jones, but, whoa, Steve Jones.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 756, "question": "You're happy with that?", "qSentId": 755}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "Can I ask you a huge favor?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111006pmt", "aSentId": 764, "question": "Can I storm off?", "qSentId": 763}]